I'm Shiva!
To have a bright future...
I was paving a path towards it.
A relation...
A twist...
Have changed my journey into a love story.
Because of the pain caused in this journey...
I'm before you today.
This Shiva143 is my journey till here.
Hey, Come!
-This place is very nice.
Good Morning sir!
Good Morning Murthy! How's everything going?
Actually sir...
Dad, I wanna play.
Okay, go and play!
-Thank you! Bye uncle!
What's the matter Murthy?
Our Kottaguda project is almost getting completed.
I've sent you the documents of Jadcherla plot.
Our office manager is not performing well sir.
If he is not efficient, hire a new one.
Okay sir!
You need not bring these small matters to me.
We have appointed him as manager,
as my son is not in a good condition.
Why is your son in such a condition sir?
Its all my fate Murthy!
One day he is coming down...
Accidentally he fell from stairs and got hit on his head.
That's it! From that he is in this condition.
I've taken him to many hospitals, but no use.
He only go to his friend doctor but no other doctor.
They come every week and give medication.
But still no use.
I earned this for him only.
I wanted to hand over him all these businesses.
But he is in this condition.
Good morning dad!
-Good morning dear!
What's the matter?
This center here is a big success.
Everyone coming here are liking it a lot.
So its going well.
Good! Atleast you are there to take off my burden.
But Murthy, we must be in one sector only.
We should step in multiple sectors at once.
Yes sir!
I'm lucky that I have a daughter
to takes good care of the things I tell her.
I forgot to ask dear.
I'm taking care of your marriage arrangements.
But how are the Sangeeth arrangements going?
Ammu already spoke to an event manager about it.
Actually I came here to tell you about that.
You mean that "Ammoru"?
No! Don't call her like that.
She gets angry by that. Just call her Ammu.
Okay! You go and take care of the meeting.
Okay dad, I'll wait there!
-Okay dear! All the best.
Murthy, let's talk our matters now.
They are Bubloo's friends.
They are very good doctors.
These are the one I'm telling you earlier.
Do something and make my son normal.
That's why we are here uncle. Where is he?
He might be some where over there.
Hey leave me. Where are you taking me?
Bubloo, please listen to me.
Its okay, now leave me.
Did you bring it?
-Yeah I did.
Give it to me.
Here it is.
When we say we are treating you, your dad is
thinking that we are giving you medicines.
He doesn't know that you are doing this.
If he comes to know that we gave a fake certificate about your behavior, he'll send us all to prison.
Are you helping me for nothing?
I'll not let that happen. Don't worry I'll take care.
Instead of taking care of your
dad's businesses, why are you doing this?
What do I do? He is asking me to go
to office and work and I don't like that.
He worked hard to earn this
and if I also work hard who'll enjoy all this?
You guys don't speak rules anymore.
If you repeat this, I'll tell my dad
everything and make sure you all go to prison.
No! Please don't do that.
This is friendship. Now take the glasses out.
You said that you'll take care
of my Sangeeth, how's it going?
It seems like this is my marriage, not yours.
I've already spoken to the
event manager he'll meet us here.
We've already finalized some themes.
He'll come and show you once.
-I know you are so sweet.
Though you are in pain because
of the broken engagement...
I gave all these things to you.
Pain? It isn't a love marriage to feel pain.
I just agreed to it, as the family match my status.
Is Ashish calling you?
He is calling. But I'm not answering.
Why do have to bother so much for such small things?
If you are a little patient,
your marriage will also be happening now.
What?
Leave that topic.
By the way, what about our groom's dance?
Our groom?
He is my groom.
Their family hired a choreographer.
So for our performance, we need to hire one.
Whoever the choreographer is...
He'll be dead in my hands.
Hi mam! Good morning.
-Good morning, please sit.
He is our event manager Sanjay!
He is the one who got you the photographer
for your pre-wedding photo shoot.
Oh is it! He did a very good job.
I'm very happy with that photoshoot.
-Thank you so much mam.
We hire only professionals mam.
Client satisfaction of utmost importance for us.
So how are the remaining arrangements going?
Hi sister!
-Hi Bubloo!
Isn't he cured yet?
We took him to many hospitals but no use.
Bubloo you shouldn't do like that. Go away and play.
So, what about the remaining arrangements?
We've mailed all the decors and light theme
samples that you like to our Vizag branch.
So two days before all the arrangements will be done.
Before two days? They were
supposed to be done a week before.
We are paying Lakhs right?
For any Sangeeth, the hall will be
given a day before for the decor.
Hey stop! Don't be rude like that.
You stay out of it. You don't know anything.
I know what to do. We have to dominate.
Whatever it may be. I shouldn't get
any bad remark anywhere.
This is my best friend's Sangeeth.
Don't worry mam!
You know that all the big events
in the city are handled by us.
Yeah I know, that's why I contacted you.
Okay mam, see you.
By the way, who is the choreographer?
Its Shiva! One of the best choreographers.
He'll meet you tomorrow.
Can he deal with rich people like us?
You'll see for yourself.
'Come! Come! Let's dance'
'Come! Come! Lets rock the floor'
'Never stop in showing your talent'
'Its only one life, so step towards success.'
'Like a untiring flood, create a new history'
'Give your life or take one to win this life'
'If you get a chance, re-write the history'
'No difficulty can stop you'
'Cross the boundaries with your courage'
'Defeat is very common'
'Patience is very important'
'Do not have any excuses'
'Don't worry about what is right and what is not'
'Give your life or take one to win this life'
Hey Mandakini, the song has come well.
Pay those dancers and upload
the song in YouTube by evening.
It will get a lot of views.
Good morning Shiva!
-Good morning sir!
I have a small event for you.
Will you do it?
-Sure sir!
Actually client's Sangeeth is in Vizag.
First the practice will be in Hyderabad
and the main event will be in Vizag.
My career started with your events sir.
I'll go where ever you ask me to go.
You'll have a meeting with the client tomorrow.
I'll send you the details and location in Whatsapp.
But be careful Shiva.
Never get angry for anything and...
Don't bring a bad reputation to my company.
Tomorrow evening we have a client meeting.
Get a nice and posh looking sports bike.
You don't worry sir, I'll get you a nice bike.
You stupid! I asked for a sports bike
and you got this brake less scooty?
If I didn't help, you'll curse me and if I did you say this.
It would have been good id you didn't help.
If the client know that we came on a
brake less bike, they'll put breaks to our payment.
Go it? Use your brain sometimes, lets go.
Flip Side?
-It is written correctly.
We came to the correct place.
Let's see if they are inside.
They said they'll be here.
Let's call them.
"Ammoru" it seems.
Hello!
-Hello mam is it Ammoru?
Shut up! This is Ammu not Ammoru. Who are you?
In Truecaller it showed Ammoru mam that's why...
I asked who are you?
I'm choreographer mam and my name is Shiva.
I'm coming from Shreyas media event management.
My manager asked me to meet you at this location.
We are waiting at the location mam.
Can't you wait until I come? Stay there I'm coming.
Why didn't she come yet?
Hello mam! This is Shiva,
celebrity trainer and top event choreographer.
Which celebrities did you train previously?
All that I've trained wanted to become
celebrities mam but they with drew in middle.
That's how perfectly our sir trains.
Do you have any sample videos of your work?
Actually I trained people mostly in other countries mam.
So I don't have client videos with us.
Because at that time the I'm getting
late for the flight so I have to rush back.
We went to a marriage in Vijayawada right?
Then how did you go to
other countries without my knowledge?
Will you shut your mouth for a while please?
Mam basically what kind of style do you prefer?
Like Salsa, Mambo, Jazz, Contemporary or Hip-hop?
Are you done with your over introduction?
Can I speak now?
You come to our place tomorrow
and show us your dance skills.
Choreography should be very nice
or else I'll change the choreographer.
I didn't hire you to do what you say.
I hired you to do what I say.
Understood?
Do you know puppet? You should be like that.
Puppet?
I don't know how we will finish this event with her.
'Money won't come that easy'
Isn't it?
You work for us and still you cheat us?
Did you know the pleasure
it gives when you hit a person?
You can't express it in words.
Oh God! It gives a different high.
Hey!
Why are you beating one of us like that?
Don't you have any common sense?
I'm paying you in every activity I do.
How can you speak to the police against me?
If you do like this, how will I trust you?
Its okay! I forgive you, go.
What? We caught him with great
difficulty and you simply leave him?
Won't you atleast respect our work?
Should I tell you something?
The qualities you have from birth,
will go only with your death.
Did you ever heard this?
No matter what we say, do you really
think these idiots will listen to it and change?
They'll not!
Hello my son!
I love you.
In every house that has talent there
will be a negative character to pull it back.
He is the negative character in our house.
Why do you still smoke and drink? Can't you leave them?
Don't go anywhere, stay home.
We spent a lot for your surgery recently.
You'll never listen to me.
You always keep telling this.
I'm going for bath, if someone comes ask them to sit.
Okay!
Do you know how it will be when Angelina Jolie
lives as a financier in the streets of Hyderabad?
She will be like this.
She is Rubina.
Stop it sister, I beg you.
Is this the way to fight?
If you hit someone, their mind shouldn't work.
My mind isn't working sister.
Aren't you all ashamed?
Are you all security for me or I'm security for you?
Its total waste to feed and pay you.
You don't talk sister!
You'll talk rules and be strict only with us.
That Shiva is not giving money since two years.
But you still pamper him a lot.
That name gives me...
Vibrations.
Hey Rakul...
I got it sister.
We are doing the same crap since two years.
Come lets get him.
Lets go!
Why are you here?
-Sister asked you to come.
I have an urgent dance class, please leave me.
We don't know all that. Sister asked you so lets go.
No! I won't come.
He won't listen, lets carry him.
Stop it! You saw me yesterday
and still you want to see me today as well.
No matter how many times I see you,
I still feel its like first time.
See Rubina, day by day
your love is becoming a torture for me.
These idiots are not giving me time to change my dress.
Hey don't act smart.
Give him respect. He is my life.
You are killing us sister.
Why don't you give the money back.
If I have money, why would I
come with you daily like this you morons.?
Tell us sister, what's the solution to this?
The only solution to this is him marrying me.
This is better than that.
She loves you that badly,
don't you have any feelings for her?
When you bring me like this, how will I get feelings?
Then what should I do?
Shall I give an idea?
All of you look up.
I know that you'll go, that's why I kept him there.
Get him inside. I'll feed him with biryani.
The reason for them to take me is...
Why did you come here?
I'm missing you and so I'm here.
I was about to come to you.
You miss me too?
That's why I came.
This is love.
Do you accept my love?
I want to discuss a serious matter with you Rubina.
My father is sick.
I should pay Four Lakhs for the surgery.
Please help me.
Since childhood, I kept on coming after you.
But you never cared me.
Now you came to me as you want money.
But still I'll lend you loan, on one condition.
You should come and meet me whenever I miss you.
If you didn't come on your own, my men will bring you.
Okay?
I have no other option than agreeing to this.
You idiots!
Do you know martial arts or what, jumping like that?
If I learnt it completely, I would have hit you here itself.
Don't you have any shame to bring me like this?
We are doing this as our sister asked us to do,
but not because we love you.
Mr. Rubina!
Tell me how far its fair to bring a
person like this without his consent?
Hey send him inside.
Why are you laughing?
I recalled something from our childhood,
do you want me to tell you my dear?
You'll anyways tell me.
When you are being mischievous in school,
teacher punished you by making you stand on bench.
So?
Then...
Wait!
Why you guys are laughing?
Our sister is laughing so we are also laughing.
Then Shiva, while standing on the bench...
Hey all lets laugh now.
When did you guys bring me here.
Will you eat sweet dear?
-No!
What about Biryani?
-No I won't!
Atleast eat Upma.
-I won't eat anything.
You bought me while I was in sleep
and asking about food, let me go.
Sit!
Hey you, come here.
How did I controlled him sister?
With respect.
I remembered another thing from childhood, shall I tell?
You go ahead sister!
Hey wait a minute. You guys get out.
Do you remember once teacher appreciated you?
Hey you all come here. Now tell me.
You failed in Hindi exam right?
Not about the exam, tell me the one about appreciation.
It is that, you always fail in Hindi exam.
Stop it!
Not this one, the appreciation one.
Its the same, you failed in the exam,
teacher pulled your pants and...
Because of the money I took, I got stuck up with her.
Why is he calling me now?
Hey dude!
-Why don't you answer my call?
My financial position is not so
good now so I didn't answer your call.
She is always taking me like a child whenever she want.
I don't know what you'll do,
I want back the money I gave you.
Then let's do one thing.
Someone from Vizag wants to buy my car.
If we deliver the car to the, we'll get some money.
From that I'll give your one Lakh.
I lend you money and you tell me the way to get it?
Understand me dude!
-Its okay! Bye.
Hey who are you?
-We are from Shreyas media sir.
Oh! Are you the food suppliers?
No sir!
Then light suppliers?
-No sir!
Then flower decorators?
-We are choreographers sir.
Oh you are those choreographers?
I can hire Prabhudeva but you know why did I hired you?
We have to encourage the youth.
-Oh! Thank you sir.
So you should perform really well.
The dance should be extraordinary.
-You'll see for yourself sir.
By the way, I forgot to tell you something.
This entire building is mine.
But I didn't ask about that sir.
You need not ask, its my duty to tell you.
Can we do our work now?
-Yeah! Go quick.
Thank you sir. Hey let's go.
Son?
-Yes dad!
While they dance, we should also
learn them and rock the dance floor.
So they'll take care of the decor.
Today is recording session, do you know that?
Yes mam! You'll record while we dance
and forward it to Megha mam's friends.
You trained them well.
-Its nothing, now watch.
Did you prepare well for a nice song?
Yes mam, I prepared well for a very nice song.
Hey Mandakini, play the music.
(Song from Telugu movie "Gang Leader")
What non-sense is this?
Its a Sangeeth in a star hotel,
not some function in a street.
Let it be dear. Audience like mass songs.
This is not a movie to have a
mass number for the audience.
This is marriage event right?
You don't know anything about this, so please be quite.
We don't know it seems, let's go.
Oh god! Its nice song, let it be.
Megha you don't know anything, don't argue.
You'll look very cheap in front of the groom's family.
I want to present you in a high level,
but you want to be this?
This is all because of you.
Wait, I'll call the event manager.
I've seen a lot of these.
Mr. Srinivas!
This guy, your choreographer...
Please mam! We'll do the way you like.
Srinivas, I'll call you later.
Tomorrow, I'll come up with a better song mam.
That's okay Shiva.
Tomorrow we'll practice for the remaining songs.
There is no practice tomorrow. I have a short film shoot.
Which short film?
The one I told you a few days back.
-Oh that! Okay.
Lets do how much we can here.
For the remaining we'll hire a choreographer in Vizag.
After three days we are going
to Vizag in the morning flight.
So if you come to the airport
at the exact time, we'll all go together.
By the way Shiva, how are you coming?
I have some important work in Vizag.
So, I'm going in my friend's car. After that I'll join you.
Okay see you there.
-Sure mam!
Mam you said that you'll give the advance cheque.
You did nothing and you want cheque?
I gave it to your manager, go and collect it.
Hey wait a minute! Put me down.
You'll always have something coming up.
Just a minute.
Who is this?
Hey Shiva! I'm your dad's friend.
Its been two months since your dad
took money from me still he didn't pay me back.
He is not even answering my calls.
Does he have the intention of giving it back?
I'll talk to my dad.
As his son, you are responsible for his debts.
I want the money immediately.
I'm not responsible for that, you deal it with him.
How can you say that? As his son you should pay me.
Did you ask me while giving him money you idiot.
Hey give respect.
I'm not in a good mood today. Tell her that I'll not come.
Hell with your mood. Our sister want to see you, come.
You and your sister will always want to see me.
Don't you understand?
He'll not listen like this. I'll tie him.
Wait! Wait!
Look for him all around.
Where did he disappear all of a sudden?
There he is. Hey stop!
You guys go that way. You go this way.
I got him!
Huh! You got me?
-Yeah, I did.
Hey! Sister asked us to not hit him.
You are following the rules well.
Come lets go!
What's the time?
Time? I don't have watch.
Oh! Ask them.
-I'll ask and come.
Hey you come, come.
Hey! Stop, stop.
What happened?
Stop it you morons. She asks you to
bring me and you guys come after me.
Neither you have brains nor she.
Why should we run like this.
Wait for five minutes, we'll dance.
What do you say?
(Song from old movie "Gentleman")
Hello Megha!
-Yeah tell me.
Gym trainer is here. We are waiting for you.
I can't come today.
Oh! Okay, bye!
Mam if you don't mind can I give you a suggestion?
Tell me.
If we do workouts in the morning,
we'll have more health benefits mam.
I'll get other instructor for the morning,
you stop coming in the evening.
No need mam. Evening is really good.
What are we doing today?
Yesterday we did upper body, today we'll do lower body.
We'll do workouts for legs.
No!
Today I'm having full body pains.
Only my hands are fine. So we'll do hands.
It will be good if we follow a systematic order mam.
This is my order.
Okay mam!
Here is the dumbbell.
20 reps per set.
Do you have any problem if I do 10?
No mam! As your wish.
I forgot. There is dance class today?
Yeah mam!
Okay then, you can go.
We'll practice on the track I've sent you.
Okay. We'll do that.
Its not like that mam.
You have to do it like this.
-I know, but its good like this.
Its good like that, but...
Then we'll do it like this.
Okay. We'll move on to next one.
Its not like that. Its like this.
But still this is good.
It feels really painful mam.
-For what?
I'm telling you its really painful.
-Okay, but for what?
If someone else ruins our work, its really painful.
Why do you have to feel sad? Are you doing it for free?
Just a sec, I'll call your manager.
As if you are doing it for free. I'll teach you a lesson.
What? What's your domination?
Pain? My foot!
As a choreographer I said that mam, nothing else.
Even though you are the choreographer,
it should happen the way I say.
Then you'll be the choreographer mam, not me.
So what do you say now?
Everything will happen the way you want from now.
Okay mam?
Then why do I need you, I can do it myself.
How is our songs choreography going?
Not good. Half of the time is
wasted in showing his creativity.
With great difficulty, only four songs were completed.
That's it? Then when will we practice?
After few days we'll go to Vizag.
I'll pay him only if he comes there
and complete the remaining songs.
He's a good dancer, I know that.
You might have caused him
trouble by interfering in his work.
I want camera.
-What for?
I'm producing a short film.
I need to get its making.
Your acting like a producer now!
Okay! There are my pre-wedding shoot photos in it.
So please don't format that memory card.
Don't worry. I'll keep it safe.
You go now, I'll call you after my work.
Bubloo you play here. I'll come in a bit.
Okay sister!
How's the shoot going?
Its almost climax mam.
Now the suicide scene is in progress.
Location is on third floor mam.
Then what are you waiting for?
We are waiting for the cameraman mam.
Okay then, I'll go to third floor then.
Manager gave me the cheque mam.
I need your sign on it.
Oh! I'm sorry Shiva.
Actually Ammu is handling
all the transactions, go and meet her.
Mam if you don't mind, can I ask you something?
Tell me Shiva.
It will be nice if you involve for your marriage.
She is torturing me for everything.
You speak to her once about his mam, please.
Okay I'll talk to her.
Mam I got the second installment cheque.
Client signature is needed at the back of the form.
If you tell me where you are,
I'll come and get your signature.
Meet me tomorrow, I'll sign it.
Tomorrow is bank holiday mam.
If you can sign it today,
the transaction will be processed.
Please help me today mam.
I'll share you the location in Whatsapp.
Come!
What a woman!
She is paying me just 20K but
her attitude is like as if she is paying me a million.
Did I hit him good?
Thank god!
Now our sir will speak. Sir carry on.
Basically Murthy...
All the humans are living like sheep.
Do you know how?
I'll tell you three points, listen.
Point one.
Parents work really hard and buy a house.
As it will be handy always.
But actually he'll not enjoy it,
neither will let his children enjoy.
And finally he'll die.
Point Two.
Will the children enjoy it after growing up?
They keep thinking that the property
cost will increase as time progresses.
Point Three!
The children of these type of parents are intelligent.
He isn't a fool not to enjoy the property.
He is enjoying the two generation's properties.
No matter how much you hit or scare me,
I'll not sell you the land.
I know you'll say this, that's why I have fourth point.
She should be here.
Where is she!
Where is she?
Here you are mam!
What happened mam? Why are they after you?
I came here to record the making of a short film.
Unexpectedly I've recorded a murder scene.
Understood!
Instead of taking this making,
you took that murder making.
Why do you interfere in everything?
I didn't do it intentionally.
-Okay, stop!
We should get out of here immediately.
I don't know how to jump.
-Its okay, jump!
Mam listen to me. If we give them
the camera, they'll not come after us.
Its Megha's camera.
We can buy a lot later. Listen to me,
lets atleast give them the memory card.
Megha's photos are in it.
Oh god! Girls and their madness for photos, huh!
Lets do one thing.
Please listen to me this time and hold this.
Hello! What do you mean?
I'm very scared.
Me too! You be quite for a while.
Turn around!
Be like that.
Is it empty?
Empty?
Now its empty.
Mam recorded it unexpectedly sir.
We live a very normal life sir.
We don't want these things.
What normal life? I have my own status, okay?
Keep your status aside for a while.
Hey! Give me that camera.
Give them the camera.
Here is the camera sir.
We are done here sir.
Sorry sir! We'll leave.
My camera!
-You please be silent!
There is no memory card in it.
Stop them!
Kill him!
Let's go in this car.
They are shooting Bubloo. Stop the car once.
If we stop now, they'll kill us.
I told you to give them the card, see now.
You asked me to come to your home, I'm right outside.
Come inside. I'm in my room upstairs.
Okay, coming.
Don't know why did she called me.
Hello mam!
Hello! Sit down.
What's the matter mam?
Its about the song selection.
Give me some latest songs.
Every song seems to be regular and routine.
You suggest me something.
You might be the choreographer,
but everything should happen as I say.
You should be like a puppet.
No problem mam. You tell us and we'll follow.
You'll be having some knowledge on it , right?
We may go accordingly.
Suggest me some very good songs.
Actually mam. We have a very less hit movies.
So, in every function they are playing the same songs.
My suggestion is that we'll go for retro.
If we have Chiranjeevi sir's and
Nagarjuna sir's old songs...
I think it will be very interesting.
What do you say?
Not a very good idea.
I thought you'll suggest me some nice ones,
but why are you suggesting me old ones?
Your opinion is useless.
It doesn't work.
I'll only think of something.
Then why do you have to ask me?
What?
If you have your opinion, why do you have to ask me?
I just asked, what's wrong in that?
That's what I'm saying.
If you have your opinion, why do you have to ask me?
You always complain about something or the other.
I know that whatever you say is for my good.
Tell me mam, what shall we do?
You are getting angry, right?
No mam!
-No mam. I'm perfect.
No! you are getting angry.
No mam! Why would I get angry?
I'm fed up with this fellow. I want to change this guy.
I'm calling your manager right now.
You are showing me a lot of attitude.
Me?
-If not me?
Why are you looking like that?
When I said that I don't know
how to jump the wall you made fun of me.
Do you think you fought like "Jackie Chan"
And you spoke something about me with Megha.
Am I torturing you?
Who me?
-What "Who me"?
You are not so innocent, okay?
Stop acting.
Mam actually what happened is...
-Shut up!
I've already wrote some songs, just see.
Here are the fake documents for the land you've asked.
In my service, this is the 48th land that you've captured.
If you occupy two more, it will half century.
Did you get them?
No we didn't.
I'll get their details.
That girl recorded the whole murder.
I want the recorded memory card along with the girl.
What! Someone recorded your illegal deeds?
Do you how risky if that goes out?
You, me and everyone here will go to prison.
I'm already tensed. Don't make me more tensed, got it?
48 missed calls!
Sorry Megha!
Driver isn't available, so I'm coming in a cab.
Coming, I'm on the way.
On your way to where? You've already missed the flight.
We are in Vizag already. Do you know that?
Why are you not answering my calls?
Why did I get the flight tickets four days in advance?
To do our shopping, right?
Now thanks to you everything is ruined.
Really sorry Megha!
I don't know what you'll do, you must be here soon.
Why are you tensed dear?
Ammu missed her flight dad.
Let me talk to her.
Hello!
-Yeah uncle.
Did you miss your flight dear?
-Yes uncle!
I will send you a good driver, come with him.
Who is that driver?
Its our choreographer.
He is coming to Vizag on some work, come in his car.
Journey with him?
No way!
No other option dear. We shouldn't care
about prestige in these circumstances.
We should get down a little when necessary.
I asked you to give my money
back and you gave me some work.
You are very intelligent.
One shot you'll clear my debt and sell your car.
Keys?
Atleast I can show off with the car in Vizag.
Why is he calling me now!
Tell me sir.
-Where are you?
I'm getting started to Vizag sir.
Ammu missed her flight in the morning.
Can you bring her here along with you?
Sorry sir, that is not part of my job.
I'm just a choreographer.
I know that you'll say this.
That's why I've already
talked to your Manager about this.
Talk all this with him.
Why do he have to do this?
See matter is closed.
Good morning sir, tell me.
Our client Ammu mam missed her flight.
Actually I'm going on my personal work sir.
I'll join them after it is completed.
Shiva stop talking rules now.
If its not okay for you, this will be our last event.
But that is not part of my job sir.
Okay fine! This will be our last event.
Its okay sir no problem.
Its just pick and drop right sir? I will take care.
I'm dead!
Hello mam, get in.
Keep my luggage in the trunk.
I'm a choreographer, not driver.
You keep it in.
Is it so!
One minute.
Got it.
I'll keep the luggage inside.
Get a water bottle on the way.
Mam shall we go?
-Yeah! Lets go.
I want water bottle.
I know mam. That's why I stopped the vehicle.
Wait for a while, I'll bring it.
Hello dear Good morning!
-Good morning dad!
You should be going to Vizag, did you reach the airport?
No dad! I missed the flight, so going by road.
I called you regarding that marriage proposal.
Daddy, I already told you.
You are important to me.
Do it the way you like.
But... You should be okay with it too.
Dad! I am okay with anything you like.
Give me a water bottle.
Boss, we have information that they are going Vizag.
We are waiting for them on the way.
As soon as we find them,
we will get the card and bring it to you.
How did you reach before I do?
Well... She said she was thirsty...
Catch him!
Hey, stop there!
What happened? How are they?
Who else? Your fans.
So much for recording and hiding it.
They now know we are going to Vizag.
If we get caught, we are dead.
I told you give them the card, but you didn't listen to me.
I told you there are Megha's photos in that card.
Oh please! You'd always say something.
I am hungry.
I said I am hungry. Why did you bring me here?
There are no star hotels anywhere near here.
Where is the waiter?
Shiva! They are watching us.
I suspect something.
It might be them.
No doubt, it is them.
Why are you coming after me instead of her?
I don't want her. We need you.
Let's go.
She is the one who recorded,
why are you taking me?
Hey, Rakul?
How did you find out?
-Why wouldn't I?
Who else will come 100 K.M.s for me? Useless idiots!
You'll kill me or what?
She asks us to bring you with out hitting.
But you keep on escaping from us.
Lets do one thing, lets eat mutton biryani and go.
She knows what to do, lets go.
Who are they?
I have an one sided love story.
Do you love someone?
No! I was being loved.
Great! There are people who love you.
Who is she?
Sweet heart!
I'm here!
When did you get in?
While you were escaping
from them like a little Krishna...
Then I got in the back seat silently.
I'm going on an important event, please leave me.
I'll be back in three days.
Oh no! I should spend three days without seeing you?
I can't!
That too with a girl.
God!
Can you come and sit in the back seat?
No! I'm comfortable here.
Now tell me!
This journey will be very beautiful, isn't it sweet heart?
My fate sucks!
Who is she?
She's Ammu mam, my client.
Client?
Yes client!
She's learning dance from me.
I asked you many times to teach me, but you didn't.
You are dancing with my life, why do I teach you again?
Eat!
You look very cute when you are angry.
Bill please!
Why did you stop here?
We ate just now so I'm feeling drowsy.
If I drive like this, we'll definitely have an accident.
If you drive non-stop, we'll reach Vizag by morning.
I'm not a bus driver to drive non-stop.
Don't torture me mam, let me sleep.
You sleep. I'll keep on looking at you the whole night.
Where is Ammu?
No matter how much you look for her you'll not find her.
Because she is with me.
You are in deep sleep last night.
So I didn't disturb you.
She knows where the card is, so we got her.
Now she says that she doesn't where the card is.
If you have any info, please tell you.
Don't do anything to her.
The card is with me.
I'll send you the location in Whatsapp.
Give me the card and take her.
Even I don't have the card.
But I should rescue her somehow.
Where is she?
Some goons kidnapped her.
We should save her.
Why should you rescue her?
She is my client and I'm going to
do choreography for their event only.
How will the event happen without her?
I don't think so.
I feel that you are showing more interest in her.
Interest? My foot!
I'm just being responsible for my client.
Is it?
She is beautiful than me, so...
You might be showing interest in her.
What? She is beautiful than you?
Tell me, Is she beautiful than you?
Tell me heartfully, is she really beautiful than you?
Just tell me frankly.
Does anyone in the world can
speak Telugu so cute like you?
Ofcourse, you are right.
Is this what you understand all these days?
Lets go sweet heart.
She'll not get convinced if I didn't say all this.
This is the location.
They might be here.
They are very dangerous. We should be very careful.
They don't know about me.
That's what I'm afraid of.
Lets go.
What's the time bro?
-I don't have a watch.
I know.
Ganesh bro!
We kidnapped the girl and kept her with us.
You don't worry at all.
Give me the phone once. I'll speak.
With great difficulty we got her boss.
What's the difficulty in getting a sleeping girl you idiot.
Somehow or the other, get the card from her.
After that kill the girl.
Understood?
-You don't worry boss.
We have Rajahmundry's Sayed bhai with us.
No one can take her from us.
Either kill her or get the card.
If not I'll kill you.
I'll not give you that chance.
I've already sent him the location.
He is coming here with the card.
I'll not leave him this time.
Okay!
I won't get angry usually.
Where is the card?
That card is not with us right now.
Again same dialogue.
Hey looks like he is here, go get him.
Lets do one thing, you go that way and I'll go this.
If you find her, get her to the car.
I'll not get her.
Please understand me, its her event.
Who are you?
Got it!
You are his girl.
Where is she bro?
You hit me for asking a question?
I can't fight these many.
Who are you?
Hey do you who am I? I'm Rajahmundry's don.
What took you so long Shiva? Get me out of here.
You stay here. Let's go.
Come, untie me.
You are commanding here as well.
Hey find them.
-Okay bro!
Lets go.
Will you leave me and go sweet heart?
Oh god! She is killing me.
Shiva you should hit the one
with big mustache really hard.
He is very arrogant you know.
He kept on asking me about the card, senseless fellow.
Hello mam, why do have to say that?
Give me the card and I'll go.
Why don't you listen to me?
Why do you keep on asking me about it?
Don't worry about the card bro. I'll tell you where it is.
Who are you and why are you always interfering?
How dare you hit my sweet heart?
They are fools Rubina, they won't listen to you.
Leave them, we'll go.
No, I'll not leave him.
She won't listen, let's go.
Hey she is still there.
They will be in danger because of her, get in.
Dude its me Shiva.
-Tell me.
I'm coming to Vizag with a girl.
We have a problem with some people.
They are chasing us.
-Chase?
Are you in love or what?
Its nothing like love.
If we have any problem,
can we stay at your house for the night?
No problem. I have a pent house,
you can stay in it as long as you want.
Hello sir!
-Hey Mandakini!
Megha mam and family are in the Vizag farm house.
You get that address and go there, okay?
Okay sir, when will you come?
-I'm in some problem.
I'll be late.
No problem sir I'll take care.
What about the remaining songs?
I'll do the remaining songs
choreography once I come there.
One more thing...
Mandakini can you hear me?
Speak!
Can you here me?
He is saying something.
What are you doing here?
Why don't you tell me before you go?
I don't have to tell you.
You should tell me.
My dying every second
fearing what might happen to you.
They took you only a while ago.
What if they come again?
I'm saving you and you are very mean to me.
My work is just choreography.
Why should I care about all these?
Taking you to Vizag and saving
you is such a waste of time.
Who asked you to save me?
I'll kill you if you saying anything rude like this.
Your right.
Why should I save you?
I don't care about you anymore.
Good bye!
How are you?
-I'm fine!
All okay?
-Everything is fine.
We'll leave 5.30 in the morning.
No problem, you can leave when ever you want.
Show her the room, she'll freshen up.
Here take the bag.
I'll kill you if you again speak rude.
Taking you to Vizag and saving
you is such a waste of time.
I don't care about you anymore, good bye.
'How did the god made you so beautiful'
Why is she crying?
What happened? Why are you crying?
How can you speak like that with a girl?
You can't talk to me like that, okay?
You should respect me.
Even my dad haven't spoke to me like that.
Yeah! That's why...
You are like this.
If your father spoke with you
the way I did long back you'll not be like this.
Respect? my foot.
But still you should respect me, right?
What do you mean by respect?
Come on tell me.
Respect is respect.
It should have some definition right?
Who will give you respect in your house?
My driver.
-And?
Our maid.
My dad's employees.
They all respect you because they work for you.
That means...
They respect you only because you pay them.
Otherwise who will respect you?
Not only them...
90% in the world will respect others
only because of their necessities.
Not because they really mean it.
I'll tell you a secret.
Come here.
I started liking you very much.
Not only that.
You looked very beautiful to me.
But no smart person will love you.
Do you know why?
Where are my eyes?
Isn't it?
Do you know where your eyes are?
They are on your head.
Didn't get it?
Due to the wealth, beauty and
arrogance your eyes are on your head.
That's why you are don't treat anyone nicely.
Once keep your eyes in their place and look.
The whole world will look beautiful.
Saying all this all my high is gone.
This is enough for today, sleep.
Its 4.30 AM!
Go get ready, we'll leave.
I need to talk to you.
Tell me.
Like you said...
Saving me is not your responsibility.
But still you are doing a lot for me.
Without noticing that, I've troubled youso much.
Not the sorry, but the last words saying trouble are...
That gave me the real high.
I bless you to stay happy and
understand me like this always.
Stop it!
'My feet started running to get to you'
'I have started writing letters on your heart from today'
'Time which used to travel fast has slowed down now'
'This journey with you, has now become thrilling'
'I have a lot of words in heart but they aren't coming out'
'Shall I tell you in a word that you are mine'
'Listen to me my dear, I love you heartfully'
'Whatever may happen, I'll live with the love on you'
'My heart beat is searching for you'
'How can I express my feelings on you'
'I am not with me till now,
ask my shadow which is after you'
'My heart started running for you'
'Listen to me my dear, I love you heartfully'
'Whatever may happen, I'll live with the love on you'
'Even though this journey started with you'
'How will I reach reach my destination with you'
'Ask every part of me which is getting together with you'
'My crazy jumping heart has started looking for you'
'Listen to me my dear, I love you heartfully'
'Whatever may happen, I'll live with the love on you'
Hey! How are the Sangeeth arrangements going?
Ammu has got a nice event manager brother.
Their pre-arrangements are really good.
Especially, the dance choreography is really good.
Oh! Is it?
There you are. He is the choreographer.
You did a really good job.
Its all Ammu mam's guidance.
I just followed it.
He became a headache to me.
Isn't he cured yet brother?
Why don 't you take him to a nice doctor?
What do I do? He'll not come to the doctor I take him.
He only let his friends treat him.
His friends are very intelligent doctors.
I know some good doctors here.
You don't worry. I'll take him to them.
They'll cure him very quickly.
Oh god! Looks like my acting will be revealed.
I need to divert them now.
Daddy!
-What?
I want a helicopter.
Helicopter?
If you get cured, I thought
of starting an airlines with you.
Hey why don't you compose a nice song for my son?
Sir actually I have an important call.
Mandakini will handle him sir.
He is better than me.
If you show your talent to people
like him you'll get better opportunities.
Mandakini if you want to become like your master,
start experimenting on my son.
Go and teach!
Comes lets dance.
I don't know when will he get normal.
I'll dance to NTR song.
We'll go to that later, first learn this.
I think he is convinced that I'm mentally ill.
Why are you looking like that.
In the condition you are now,
you want to dance to NTR songs?
God is really bad. He gave this much wealth to you.
If I were this rich...
Its okay leave all that and do what I say.
Why did you call me?
What if someone see us?
Let them see. We can't hide anything for long, right?
I'll tell them.
What will you say?
I'll tell that...
Nothing!
Evening everyone is going out to
distribute wedding cards.
No one will be home.
Should I go with them or stay?
Don't go.
Why?
Nothing!
I think no one is home?
Why are you looking at the moon like that?
I never felt that moon is beautiful before.
First time its looking really beautiful.
When in love, everything looks beautiful.
What?
Nothing!
I need to tell you something.
Don't tell me anything that disturbs my mood.
Tell them later.
I'm really very happy now.
Okay then, tell about youself.
Nothing much to tell.
Nothing!
I'm just living a normal life, working hard.
Tell me about your parents.
My parents?
There's nothing to say about my dad.
I love my mother very much.
Mom left me in my childhood by committing suicide.
I'm just living with her memories.
Did you ever love someone?
Love? No way!
I spent my whole life running after responsibilities.
I didn't have the luxury to love someone.
What would happen even if I love?
It will be just some messages and calls.
What sort of girl do you want?
The girl should replace my mother with her love.
What should be done to make you feel like that?
It will be only my expectation.
Not possible.
But first time...
I felt like that after seeing a girl.
I never felt like that before.
After getting close to you, I felt that.
I thought of telling it to you first.
But you did it first.
No don't!
Don't spoil your good impression.
Lets sleep today by watching the moon.
Stay where you are.
Be calm.
You didn't complete my song yet.
Will you teach me a new song?
Why should I teach you?
You don't understand anything and
your father won't listen to me.
I'm dying in middle.
Why are you looking like that?
You hit me? You look normal too.
Normal? Of course I'm normal.
I'm acting like this as I don't want to
get into my father's business.
You try to command me?
My range is like Pawan Kalyan
in "Attarintiki Dharedhi" movie.
But you try to boss me by
teaching some dance moves?
You try to boss me?
I'm cheating my dad by bringing
some fake certificates from doctors.
And passing my time by having few pegs.
Now you come and command me?
Its not fair to cheat a wonderful father like him.
Why are you worried so much as if he is your father?
Fathers are there to earn.
And sons are there to enjoy that.
You don't tell me any new rules, got it?
Be careful.
We are just playing.
The first mistake I did is to raise you
by giving what ever you want.
If I knew that you'll be like this,
I would have earned only for myself.
Unnecessarily I've worked hard
to earn all these to give you.
If you didn't come to office
from tomorrow, I'll see your end.
I'll see why won't you take up the business.
Great timing bro!
Looks like I was here to get you smashed.
We are sad that we don't have a dad that earns like this.
You have a dad that earns well and you are like this.
What sort of life is this?
Shiva get ready in five minutes, we'll go out.
Why?
I want to talk to you.
Why do we need to go out for that, lets talk here.
Its personal Shiva.
What's personal?
Personal means personal, go get ready.
I won't come.
-You won't come?
No!
But why?
There are some rules for me to come.
What are the rules?
You should understand when I say rules.
Got it.
Not that.
-Then what?
I want the one we missed last night.
You have a lot of movie influence on you, get ready.
All the Telugu movies are like this now-a-days.
Huh! I need to get ready!
Hey Shiva! How's the choreography going?
Choreography is done sir.
-Then when are you leaving?
I have a small work here,
so I might go tomorrow or the day after.
One minute sir I have to make a call.
Thank god you got dressed, lets go to shopping.
My friend is admitted in hospital,
so I'm going to meet her.
What friend you have in Vizag that I don't know about?
She's my cousin's friend.
She helped me a lot once,
so I should go and see her atleast once.
Okay come, I'll drop you.
I've already booked a cab.
It will come to the Banquet at the end of this street.
I'll go then.
-Okay, go!
Hello Mister!
We came here to have a happy time together,
but why are you so serious?
If we get married everyone will say
that I married you only for your money
I thinking of the ways to handle that.
Shiva! Why do we have to care what others think?
I'll tell my dad about us, as soon as I reach home.
But before that I need to tell you something.
Not now, we'll talk later.
Please listen to me once Shiva.
What happened? Did she say anything?
Nothing!
Did you kill him or what?
No brother!
Wake him up.
Where is Ammu?
I've killed her. What will you do about it?
Don't lie. She is my sweet heart.
I'll break all your bones and take her from here.
He's out of control.
Hey hit him with rods.
Come, come rascals!
Looks like he'll kill us.
I should get the girl.
Sir, please stop. I'm sending her.
You are asking about him and he is asking about you.
Mam, go.
Or else sir will kill us.
Its okay, don't cry!
What happened? Why are you crying?
He threatened me a lot.
Who?
This guy.
How can you be so harsh on her?
What?
I didn't do or say anything to her.
I swear,.
You are complaining about me unnecessarily.
My boss is calling.
I don't know what to tell him.
Give it to me.
I saved her even though she is
not an important person in my life.
Now she is very important part of my life.
If you again come after her...
I'll not leave you
We've come here on an important work.
After its finished, I'll come and give you the card.
If you still disturb us...
You can't imagine what my next move will be.
Oh god!
Did it hurt bad?
Its all for you, so I don't have any pain.
Its yours.
One minute, its bluetooth.
Hi dear! How are you?
Hi dad! I'm fine, how are you?
I'm fine dear.
Why didn't you call me since a week, Are you busy?
Yes dad!
Okay! The matter is
you said okay to a marriage proposal, right?
They keep on pushing me about it.
If you come early, we'll do the remaining arrangements.
When are you coming back?
I've already asked Megha's dad to inform you about this.
Did he inform you?
Dad I'll call you back.
Why didn't you tell me that your marriage got fixed?
I didn't accept the marriage out of interest in it.
After you came into my life...
Don't tell me.
I understood.
You said okay to it and here you are
having me as a temporary boy friend.
Don't talk like that Shiva.
Then what should I speak?
You asked me a question,do you remember?
If I was in love ever.
Never!
You know why?
I don't have the guts to take this pain.
But you gave me more than the pain I've imagined.
Listen to me Shiva!
Don't talk.
From now, we will not be together.
You go first.
They'll suspect.
Shiva please.
Listen to me once.
-No I won't.
Please Shiva.
-I won't listen.
Wait I need to talk to you.
How Megha and you are best friends...
Me and your dad are also same.
The matter is that you are not at all
showing interest in the proposal you've agreed.
When we do an event...
Photographer, Choreographer, DJ are all options.
We can change them whenever we want.
But the proposal father got you is not an option dear.
So you should agree with your parents.
It will be good for everyone.
We should always try to multiply our respect and wealth.
Not to diminish them.
I hope you understand why I'm saying all this.
Shiva wait. I need to talk to you.
Here is your payment of one Lakh.
I'm giving you extra fifty thousand.
Do you know why?
For you to not come back.
You grow by working hard.
But its not correct to trap a
rich girl and become rich over night.
Is she you daughter?
She is like my daughter. So what?
If I worked only as a choreographer...
She'll won't be with you now.
Ask her the reason for that.
I'll never have the thought of
getting rich the way you said.
Take back your cheque.
I never thought that I'll be an option in someone's life.
Every youngster will fall in love at come point in life.
But whomever they love,
they'll be left with tragedy at the end.
This is my story till now.
Let's see how it will be in future.
Tell me sir, you asked me to come.
All the Telugu associates in
Singapore are planning some events.
There is a need for a choreographer in that.
If you are okay with that, I'll talk to them.
You should bare all the expenses including tickets.
If its okay for you...
I'll talk to them.
Sure sir!
Thank you so much for giving me this offer.
I'll arrange the money soon and contact you.
What happened there Shiva?
Nothing sir, a small accident.
Okay Shiva all the best. See you soon.
Why are you looking at me like that my son?
Is it because I was drunk?
Every house should have a hard working son like you.
Then only father can happily relax like me.
One should have luck for all that dad.
You are very lucky.
I have a doubt dad.
Do you have any shame in you?
When your son is working hard,
you are passing the time by getting drunk daily.
Did you ever ask yourself about how hard I'm working?
Why should I? As a son, its your responsibility.
I'm correcting all the mistakes you've done.
Do you know how hard and painful it is?
No son whose has some goals, have a father like you.
If the government gets a rule
to kill all the father's like you...
I'll be the first person to be happy.
Don't you know the rule to respect your parents?
Even animals have children.
But it doesn't make them parents.
Parents are those who are responsible.
In every house, father's are the strength.
But you are a big minus for me.
My mom, who left me with her
memories by committing suicide and you...
Will never mean anything to me.
How can you leave me and go dear?
I came all the way there only for you.
I'll leave if you don't like me.
How many times did I tell you that I don't like you?
But you still don't get it.
You want marriage, right?
You said it many times.
I'll also become a financier like you for living.
Because people like me shouldn't have goals.
Tell after you've finished all the arrangements.
I'll compromise and live with you.
This site is the only memory of your mother left.
You want to sell it?
Think about it once.
No other option.
Sometimes to grow in life...
We have to do something like this.
After going there I'll send you money every month.
Take care of my father.
Then what about me?
How did she come here?
Where is you sir? He's not answering my calls.
You want to talk to him, right?
I'll take care don't worry.
I've sent the location to her sir.
You always do useless things well, Mandakini.
Then what should I do sir?
Why always everyone should listen to you?
Why don't you listen to them?
You should give a chance to others too.
She is trying to call you many times.
You won't listen to her.
Why are you rising your voice?
You both talk, I'll leave.
I'll deal with you later Mandakini.
I've heard a lot like this.
Even he is harsh with me.
Please listen to me once Shiva.
I won't!
Will you listen or not?
-No I won't.
You won't listen?
What are you doing?
What's this assault?
What, assault?
You broke up with me and went away
without even listening to me.
What do you call that then?
You told me to look with my eyes down and
the world looks very beautiful.
From that day, you became my world unnoticeably.
I tried many times to tell you this, but you never let me.
You went away from me but I'm having the punishment.
She's right.
I should hit you hard.
Okay!
Who is it at this time?
Hey where is the card?
Card? What card?
Wedding card?
We patched up just now.
After the marriage got fixed, I'll send you the first card.
I'm asking about the memory card.
Memory card? I already gave it.
To whom?
Of course to the police.
They must be on the way to your house.
After all these fights and chases
why would I give it to you ?
They might me on the way, don't worry.
Who is that?
Who else.
Your fans. Sorry, our fans.
He gave the card to the Police?
I expected it.
Okay! Lets have lunch.
Why are looking like that?
Prison food will not be good.
So lets have lunch and go.
Stay here Shiva.
I'll come in five minutes after that we'll go out.
After marriage every word seems very sweet.
I'm feeling shy!
Why these idiots are coming?
Why you guys are here?
I think you are missing me a lot.
Its nothing like that.
Looks like you've settled well after marriage.
Of course I did.
As if I was working in a sports academy
you always keep on chasing me.
Half of my life is wasted with that.
Its all gone now.
I gave all the money back.
With interest in a single payment.
All the Villas from here to there are mine.
I can live with their rents.
This seems good.
As you came here anyway, lets have lunch.
We didn't come here for lunch.
We are here to take you.
They started it again.
You are not getting it.
That episode is done, okay?
So please go away from here.
Listen to me first.
You said some sentimental dialogues to our sister.
She became mad and got admitted in the hospital.
She is always mad and you joined her.
You kept on doing whatever she says.
This property belongs to my wife now.
I'm married now.
I'm officially husband to my wife.
So you need my wife's permission for anything.
Tell me.
Meet my wife Ammu.
She is very good, not like your sister.
See Ammu, they are trying to take me.
Tell them that this husband belongs to you.
Take him.
What's wrong? Why did you tell them to take me?
What should I do?
You tortured me a lot without answering my calls.
I had to solve all my problems.
In the same way, you solve your problems now.
Don't bring your problems to me please.
This is wrong Ammu.
They already came to me and took permission.
You take him guys.
-Thank you sister.
This is not fair Ammu.
I'm your husband Ammu.
This is very injustice Ammu.